<Document>
  # MOBILE CLINIC: CALADRIUS
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MedicalTechFab"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CryoPod"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MedicalBed"/>
  </Box>

    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Large

	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 3-4

	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Plasma

	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None

	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  "A body with the functionality of an entire clinic packed onto a single vessel. Capable of nearly everything that is required in the medical field with additional room for growth. This class is deployed throughout troublesome sectors with large casualty statistics after the design was released to the public and promptly outsourced in droves."

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  ## 1. Power supply

  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the SKR CR-class Z-pinch nuclear fusion reactor unit is connected to the cable terminal.
  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that all APC unit's Main Breakers are toggled on.

  ## SKR CR-class Z-pinch nuclear fusion reactor.
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GeneratorCRPinch"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FuelPlasma"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerPowerMonitoring"/>
  </Box>

  - [color=#e9d502][bold]Wear protective equipment due to radiation leakeage.[/bold][/color]
  - Check that the generator unit is connected to the cable terminal of your SMES via HV.
  - Check the fuel remaining of the generator unit.
  - Enable Injection.

  ## 2. Atmospherics

  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>

  - Ensure O2 and N2 canisters are anchored to mixer connector ports.
  - Check that the mixer settings are suitable (~22% oxygen, ~78% nitrogen, 101.325 kpa).
  - Enable the gas mixer.

  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasVentScrubber"/>
  </Box>

  - The ships waste loop is automated using scrubbers and a passive vent in space.
  - Make sure the scrubbers are linked to a rooms air alarm.

  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameCaution"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the thrusters are powered, and enabled.**

  ## 4. Cryogenics setup. 
 
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CryoPod"/>
  </Box>

  - This guide only covers the bare minimum of the cryopod's many possible setups.
  - Set the freezer unit to a low number. Ask around for the optimal temperature.
  - Activate the distribution pump with a survivable pressure value and then deactivate it after a short amount of time to give the Cryogenics unit an air supply (Use the gas analyzer to make sure its around 100kpa.)
  - Activate the gas filter that connects to the waste line and have it filter the gases you want to keep so that it goes back into the cryopod's loop (That means make it filter the things you WANT the patient breathing in.)
  - Insert a beaker of Cryoxadone into the Cryopod.
  - Test it on yourself or a willing person!

  ## Sidenotes

  * - The Caladrius is equipped with a storage bay toward the bow of the ship for use within the crew's discretion. The bay is also home to the ship's shields system and some other engineering related equipment.
  
  ** - There are shutters throughout the ship that can be toggled using their respective buttons.

</Document>
